dallascounty.org 2012-05-29

# Dallas County, Texas

| Dallas County Help Center  
---  
Contact Us  
  
Employment  
  
Emergency Preparedness  

Newsletters  
  
Online Services  
  
Public Information Office  
  
Report a Concern   

Top Searches  
---  

Stay Connected  
---  

* * *

Thank you for visiting the Dallas County Online Portal. This website is designed to make it easier and more efficient for Dallas County citizens and businesses to interact with their local government. Like all online resources, we recognize that visitors to this website are concerned about their privacy. Dallas County is committed to preserving your privacy when visiting this website. 

This policy describes the County's privacy practices regarding information collected from visitors to this website. This policy describes what data is collected and how that information is used. The County may, at its sole discretion, change, modify, add, or delete portions of this policy. Because this privacy policy applies only to this website, you may wish to examine the privacy policy of any website, including other local websites you access through this website. 

**Information Collected When You Visit this Website**

When visiting this website the County automatically collects and stores the following information about your visit: 

  1. The Internet Protocol address and domain name of your Internet service provider. The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer, which can be used to direct internet traffic to you; 
  2. The type of browser and operating system you used; 
  3. The date and time you visited this site; 
  4. The web pages or services you accessed at this site; and 
  5. The URL or web site address of the web site you visited prior to coming to this website and from which any web page on this site was linked. 

This information is used to improve this website's content and to help the County understand how people are using this website. This information is collected for statistical analysis, to determine what information is of most and of least interest to our visitors, and to identify system performance or problem areas. The information is not collected for commercial marketing purposes and the County does not sell or distribute the information collected from the Portal for commercial marketing purposes. 

**Information Collected When You Email this Website**

If during your visit to this website you send an email to the County, your email address and the contents of your email will be collected. 

The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats you send us. 

Your email address and the information contained in your email may be used to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to further improve this website, or to forward your email to another agency for appropriate action. Your email address is not collected for commercial marketing purposes and the County does not sell or distribute your email address for commercial marketing purposes. 

**Personal Information and Choice**

"Personal information" is information about an individual (e.g. an individual's name, address, and phone number). A domain name or Internet Protocol address is not considered personal information. 

Personal information is not collected through this website unless you send an email containing such information to the County through this website. If you do not communicate with this website it does not affect your ability to use any other features of this website or other government websites. 

The County does not knowingly collect personal information from children or create profiles of children through this website. People are cautioned that the collection of personal information provided by any individual in an email will be treated the same as information given by an adult, and may, if not protected by federal or State law, be subject to public access. The County encourages parents and teachers to be involved in children's Internet activities and guide the children whenever children are asked to provide personal information on-line. 

**Disclosure of Information Collected Through This Website**

Information collected through this website, personal or otherwise, may, if not protected by local, federal or state law, be subject to disclosure pursuant to law, such as the Freedom of Information Law (FOIL), or court order. 

Additionally, the County may disclose personal information to local, federal or state law enforcement authorities to enforce its rights against unauthorized access or attempted unauthorized access to the County's information. 

**Security**

The County limits employee access to personally identifiable information from this website to only those employees who need access to perform a specific job. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation, and day-to-day operations of this website as part of our continuing commitment to the security of electronic content as well as the electronic transmission of information. 

**NOTE:** The information contained in this policy should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof the security of information provided via this website. For site security purposes and to ensure that this website remains available to all users, the County employs software to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to this website. 

**Links Disclaimer**

In order to provide visitors with certain information, this website provides links to local, state and federal government agencies, and websites of other organizations. A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint, accuracy, opinions, policies, products, services, or accessibility of that website. Once you link to another website from this website, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that website.

**Information Disclaimer**

Information provided on this website is intended to allow the public immediate access to public information. While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current, and reliable information, the County recognizes the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Therefore, the County, its employees, officers and agencies make no representations as to the accuracy, completeness or suitability of the information provided by this website, and deny any expressed or implied warranty as to the same. 

**Language Translation Disclaimer**

The information on Dallas County's web site is originally published in English. Sections of the web site use free translation software that allows for real-time translation of information into other languages. Translations from English may not always be accurate or precise. Dallas County does not warrant such translations and disclaims any responsibility, including all alleged direct and consequential damages, for inaccurate translations. Readers relying on precise information should check the original English versions.

**Contact Information**

For questions regarding the Privacy Policy please contact: [webmaster@dallascounty.org](mailto:webmaster@dallascounty.org)

| 

| Most Visited  
---  
Criminal Background Search  
Online Record Search  
Jail Lookup  
Public Access to Court Records  
Dallas County Wanted  
Jury Services  
Property Tax Lookup/Payment Application  
Online Services  
Marriage and Official Public Records Search  
Human Resources  
Dallas County Clerk  
Make Payments to Dallas County  
Marriage License  
Dallas County’s Employment Section  
Top Searches  
---  
Complete Calendar...
